https://www.concordant.org/about/terms-of-service/

Skip to content
My Account
Please enter your name and email below to acess our audio downloads.
Name
Email
X
Welcome to the Concordant Publishing Concern website, (CPC).  The following Terms of Service apply when you view or use the CPC website,  or by accessing the CPC website on your mobile device.  Please review the following terms carefully. By accessing or using CPC website, you signify your agreement to these Terms of Service. If you do not agree to these Terms of Service, you may not access or use the CPC website.  Violations of these TERMS OF SERVICE should be reported via email to legal@concordant.org
PRIVACY POLICY
The CPC respects the privacy of its users. Please refer to the Privacy Policy which explains how we collect, use, and disclose information that pertains to your privacy. When you access or use the CPC website, you signify your agreement to this Privacy Policy.
USE RESTRICTIONS AND COPYRIGHTS The content on concordant.org is representative of many years of work by those closely involved with CPC.  It is available to computer and mobile device users all over the world, but we guard it carefully as the ministry God has given to us.  Therefore, items available on our website are available for personal use only.  Distribution of materials either in electronic form or printed form is strictly prohibited.  Any website is free to link to our CPC pages, but never to copy and display CPC content on their own website.  CPC respects the intellectual property rights of others and we kindly request that others respect our wishes. Pursuant to 17 U.S.C. 512(i) of the United States Copyright Act.  Please report any violation to: legal@concordant.org
LINKS TO OTHER SITES AND/OR MATERIALS
CPC may provide you with convenient links to third party website(s) (“Third Party Sites”) as well as content or items belonging to or originating from third parties (the “Third Party Applications, Software or Content”). These links are provided as a courtesy.  CPC has no control over Third Party Sites and Third Party Applications, Software or Content or the promotions, materials, information, goods or services available on these Third Party Sites or Third Party Applications, Software or Content. Such Third Party Sites and Third Party Applications, Software or Content are not investigated, monitored or checked for accuracy, appropriateness, or completeness by the Company, and the Company is not responsible for any Third Party Sites accessed through the Site or any Third Party Applications, Software or Content posted on, available through or installed from the Site, including the content, accuracy, offensiveness, opinions, reliability, privacy practices or other policies of or contained in the Third Party Sites or the Third Party Applications, Software or Content. Inclusion of, linking to or permitting the use or installation of any Third Party Site or any Third Party Applications, Software.
Content does not imply approval or endorsement thereof by CPC. If you decide to leave the Site and access the Third Party Sites or to use or install any Third Party Applications, Software or Content, you do so at your own risk and you should be aware that our terms and policies no longer govern. You should review the applicable terms and policies, including privacy and data gathering practices, of any site to which you navigate from the Site or relating to any applications you use or install from the site.
MODIFICATION OF TERMS OF SERVICECPC can amend these Terms of Service at any time and will update these Terms of Service in the event of any such amendments. It is your sole responsibility to check the Site from time to time to view any such changes in the Agreement. If you continue to use the Site, you signify your agreement to our revisions to these Terms of Service.
These Terms of Service and your use of the Site are governed by the federal laws of the United States of America and the laws of the State of Michigan, without regard to conflict of law provisions.
CPC may assign or delegate these Terms of Service and/or the Company’s Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, to any person or entity at any time with or without your consent.
YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ THESE TERMS OF USE, UNDERSTAND THE TERMS OF SERVICE, AND WILL BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. YOU FURTHER ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THESE TERMS OF SERVICE TOGETHER WITH THE PRIVACY POLICY REPRESENT THE COMPLETE AND EXCLUSIVE STATEMENT OF THE AGREEMENT BETWEEN US AND THAT IT SUPERSEDES ANY PROPOSAL OR PRIOR AGREEMENT ORAL OR WRITTEN, AND ANY OTHER COMMUNICATIONS BETWEEN US RELATING TO THE SUBJECT MATTER OF THIS AGREEMENT.
Pursuant to 17 U.S.C. 512(i) of the United States Copyright Act.  Please report any violation to: legal@concordant.org
Featured Literature
The Soul and the Unseen
and The Gehenna of Fire
The true significance of the word “soul,” and a critical analysis of the various terms commonly mistranslated or otherwise associated with “hell.”
Download
Order Booklet
Copyright © 2020 Concordant Publishing Concern • All Rights Reserved    Privacy Policy | Terms of Service
Website by Reedy Designs
Scroll Up
